# Akshat Gupta

#### Student Developer

I am an experienced programmer with a demonstrated history of working in the computer software industry. I'm skilled in C++, HTML and Python. I feel I am a strong business development professional with an aim to collaborate in Web Development related projects and explore the field of Machine Learning. I am also interested and experienced in Digital Marketing.



🔀 akshatvg23@gmail.com

Chennai, India

in linkedin.com/in/akshatvg

facebook.com/akshatvg

akshatvg

instagram.com/akshatvg

9600093179

akshatvg.com

@akshatvg

github.com/akshatvg

medium.com/@akshatvg

### **EDUCATION**

### **High School**

Chinmaya Vidyalaya 🗷

05/2009 - 05/2018

Courses

 PCM with Computer Science

### University

Vellore Institute of Technology, Vellore

06/2018 - Present

Courses

Information Technology

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# **SEO & Digital Marketing Intern**

FindMind Analytics Pvt Ltd

06/2019 - 08/2019

- Incharge of the company's social media channels which includes ideating, planning, coordination and posting content on Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, Instagram (stories as well as posts).
- Incharge of Search Engine Optimisation for LegalMind, a product by FindMind Analytics.

Contact: Harsh Vardhan - +91 9790650071

### Web Development Intern

Bariflo Labs 🗷

07/2019 - Present

Tasks

• Revamping the company's website.

Contact: Mr. Mrityunjay - +91 7328021033

### **SKILLS**

Leadership

**Public Speaking** 

HTML/ CSS/ JavaScript/ Bootstrap

WordPress

Medium

Digital Marketing

Management

### **PROJECTS**

magiCode (05/2019 – Present) 🗹

Voice to Code educative assistant to help migrate to new programming languages. Won IBM Challenge at AngelHack Bangalore 2019.

Common Entry Test (01/2019 – 08/2019) 🗹

Web Application to make club and chapter recruitments easier in

AAGS- Warehouse Management System (03/2019 - 03/2019)

Project to make an intelligent warehouse management system. Won VinHack 2019.

### **ORGANIZATIONS**

Developer Student Clubs VIT (12/2018 – Present) Project Manager

CodeChef- VIT (12/2018 – Present) 🗹

Technical Member

Apple Developers Group (12/2018 − 08/2019) 🗹 Technical Member

Model United Nations Society VIT (12/2018 - 06/2019)

Core Member

### **LANGUAGES**

**Enalish** 

Hindi

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Limited Working Proficiency